{
    "subject": "resource/Inseminoid",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of Inseminoid is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9537433981895447,
            "question": "Is English the primary language of Inseminoid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9056679606437683,
            "question": "Is written English used by Inseminoid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9036864638328552,
            "question": "Does Inseminoid understand spoken English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8617984056472778,
            "question": "What language does Inseminoid speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8553853631019592,
            "question": "Can Inseminoid communicate in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8404179215431213,
            "question": "Besides English, does Inseminoid speak any other languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.811147928237915,
            "question": "What are the implications of Inseminoid speaking English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7696995735168457,
            "question": "How proficient is Inseminoid in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7509927749633789,
            "question": "Does Inseminoid use slang or specialized vocabulary in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5149936676025391,
            "question": "What is the communication method of Inseminoid?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Inseminoid is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8999_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Inseminoid use slang or specialized vocabulary in English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8999_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How proficient is Inseminoid in English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8999_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the implications of Inseminoid speaking English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8999_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8999_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple. Specifically, it is stated in several files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8999/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt) that \"Language English\" for Inseminoid."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, specifically within `15.txt`, which states that the film's main language is English."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}